ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and The Cambridge Tailoring Company, 1977 (Box 106, Folder 31)
- New York Joint Board and Capitol Coat Front Co, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 106, Folder 32)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Caribe Laces, 1961 (Box 106, Folder 33)
- Puerto Rico, Local #759 and Caribe Seat Cover Corp., 1960-1961 (Box 106, Folder 34)
- California Joint Board and Carolyn Shoe Co., 1984 (Box 106, Folder 35)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Center City Manufacturing Co., 1966 (Box 106, Folder 36)
- New York Joint Board and Central Park Design Dist., Ltd., 1978-1979 (Box 106, Folder 37)
  Bushelmen
- New York Joint Board and Centre Clothes, Inc., 1963 (Box 106, Folder 38)
- Southern California Joint Board and Certified Uniform Rental Service, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 39)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Channel Ltd., 1965-1969 (Box 106, Folder 40)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Charming Glove Co., 1966-1969 (Box 106, Folder 41)
- Alabama, Chant om Manufacturing Co., 1962-1964 (Box 106, Folder 42)
- New York Joint Board and Chester Pants Corp., 1977 (Box 106, Folder 43)
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Local #111 and Chic Maid Knitting Mills, 1955-1985 (Box 106, Folder 44)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Chicago Uniform Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1977-1988 (Box 106, Folder 45)
- Massachusetts, Local #845 and Chicopee Coat Co., Inc., 1962-1976 (Box 106, Folder 46)
- Vancouver, Apparel and Related Workers' Union Local #178 and Claymore Clothes Ltd., 1970-1978 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and Cluett-Peabody & Co., Inc., 1989 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Montreal Joint Board and Canadian Children's Wear Co., Ltd., 1975-1987 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Montreal Joint Board, Local #738 and Coat Front Contractors Ltd., 1967 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union, Local #111 and College Knitting Mills, Inc., 1962-1985 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Wilshire Manufacturing Company, 1954-1976 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board and Columbia Men's Shop (Paul's), 1978 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Compania de San Lorenzo, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- Montreal Joint Board and Confection Alger, Inc., 1980 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Montreal Joint Board and Confection J.E. Caron Ltd., 1980 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  French
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Connellsville Sportswear Company, 1947-1982 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- Chicago Joint Board and Continental Slipper Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1959-1969 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Tennessee, Continental Sportswear, Inc. (Quality Apparel Corp.), 1965-1970 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Corama Fashions, Ltd., 1977 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- Consolidated Glove Cutters and Shavers Union Local #1714 and Corium Company, 1967 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- New York Joint Board and Wallace Corning of Yonkers, Inc., 1978 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- New Jersey, Local #158 and Cortefiel de Espana-Tri-Sportswear, Inc., 1968-1977 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Coverall Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1969 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- Montreal Joint Board and Les Creations Lydia, 1984-1988 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Southern California Joint Board and Crenshaw Village Cleaners, 1976-1984 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- New York Joint Board and Crestline Clothing, Inc., 1977 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- Chicago Joint Board and Cutter-Cravat, Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and D. & A. Sportswear Corp., 1972-1976 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and D & D Shirt Company, 1976-1988 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- Michigan, Midwest Regional Joint Board and IM Dach Company, 1960-1966 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- New York Joint Board and Damian Clothes, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 107, Folder 26)
- Southern Organizational Dept. and Damon International (Black Rock Manufacturing Corp.), 1966-1982 (Box 107, Folder 27)
- Chicago Joint Board and Dan-Jac, Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 107, Folder 28)
- Southern California Joint Board and Desert Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1966-1977 (Box 107, Folder 29)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Mario Di Santo, Inc., 1977 (Box 107, Folder 30)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Charles Dobbs Ltd., 1975 (Box 107, Folder 31)
- New York Joint Board and Dofson Clothes, Inc., 1972-1985 (Box 107, Folder 32)
- Vancouver, Apparel and Related Workers' Union Local #178 and Drapeshire Clothes Ltd., 1973-1978 (Box 107, Folder 33)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Clothing Workers Joint Board and Dublin Pants Co., 1963-1965 (Box 107, Folder 34)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Dubonnet Glove Co., 1966-1969 (Box 107, Folder 35)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Dudeck, Inc., 1984 (Box 107, Folder 36)
- Montreal Joint Board, Local #738 and Duroform Shoulder Pad Corp., 1967-1970 (Box 107, Folder 37)
- Tennessee, E & W of Dover, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Alabama, Eagle of Alabama, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and John Edwards Men's Shop, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board and Edwards New York Ltd., 1978 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and M. Ehrenberg Sons, Inc., 1977 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board and Eisenberg & Eisenberg, 1972-1981 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Montreal Joint Board and Electro-Knit Fabrics Ltd., 1979-1981 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Winnipeg Joint Council, Local #459 and Electro-Knit Fabrics, 1971-1979 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Eleven-Eleven Corporation, 1967-1973 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Ellison Clothes, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Connecticut, Local #125 and Elm City Shirt Co., Inc., 1953-1977 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Alabama, Elocin Apparel Corporation, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Washington, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #71 and Emil the Taylor, 1961 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Southern California Joint Board and Encino Cleaners, 1976-1982 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Energy Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1961-1986 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  St. Paul, MN
- Minnesota Joint Board and Energy Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Alcan Manufacturing Co.), 1976-1989 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  Centuria, WI
- New York Joint Board and Rosa Englander, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #667 and Enterprise Mattress co., 1981-1986 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and Everett Sportswear Co., 1955-1965 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, Local #685 and Excello, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  Seymour, IN
- New York Joint Board and F & F Clothes Shop, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and DHJ-Facemate Corp., 1969-1979 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- Connecticut, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #115 and Fairfield Department Store, 1965-1976 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Famous Clothing Co., 1977 (Box 108, Folder 24)
- Massachusetts, Local #117 and Famous Sportswear Co., 1956-1966 (Box 108, Folder 25)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board and Fashion Made Trousers, Inc., 1963 (Box 108, Folder 26)
- Chicago Joint Board and Fashions by Jack Kaye, Ltd., 1977 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union and Fastway, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 108, Folder 28)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #362 and Federal's, Inc., 1965-1978 (Box 108, Folder 29)
- Central States Joint Board, Local #518 and Federal's, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 108, Folder 30)
- New Jersey, Local #158 and Feinerman & Co., 1971-1974 (Box 108, Folder 31)
- New York Joint Board and Fenton Hall, Inc., 1977 (Box 108, Folder 32)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and The New Si Ferber, 1968-1973 (Box 108, Folder 33)
- New York Joint Board and Finecraft Coat Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 108, Folder 34)
- New Jersey, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #195 and Joe Fischman, Inc., 1980 (Box 108, Folder 35)
- Southern California Joint Board and Flair Cleaners, Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 108, Folder 36)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Flushing Shirt Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1975-1985 (Box 108, Folder 37)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and Fowler, Dick & Walker, 1968-1973 (Box 108, Folder 38)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Frank Brothers Footwear, Inc. - Fenn-Feinstein, 1960-1971 (Box 108, Folder 39)
- Southern California Joint Board and L.J. Frankel Manufacturing Co., 1977-1987 (Box 108, Folder 40)
- Tennessee, Franklin Apparel Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1978 (Box 108, Folder 41)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Garry Fredricks, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 42)
- Virginia, Local #88 and Friedman Marks Clothing Co., 1965-1975 (Box 108, Folder 43)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and John E. Fuchs Glove Corp., 1966-1972 (Box 108, Folder 44)
- New York Joint Board and G & I Men's Clothing, Inc., 1978 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and G.M. Fashions, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Connecticut, Local #125 and Gant, Inc., 1949-1969 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Gant of Texas, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Capitol District Joint Board and Gant, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- General Office and Gant, Inc., 1965-1977 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Southern Department and Gant Eagle Corp., 1979-1990 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  Salisbury, MD
- Connecticut, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #115 and Garston's, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- New York Joint Board and George's Cambridge Shop, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #113 and Giglio Coat Shop, 1977-1978 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board and Gill Manufacturing Corp., 1962-1974 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Glick & Levine, 1960-1969 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board and Glove City Abrading Co., 1963-1990 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- New Jersey, Local 2H and Gold Star Hat & Cap Co., 1983 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Goldberg's Fashion Forum, 1980-1981 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board and Golden Edge Fabrics, Inc., 1971 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Goldring, Inc., 1981 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Louis Goldsmith, Inc., 1963-1977 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Gordon Clothes, Inc., 1974-1985 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Gordon & Ferguson Co., 1966-1987 (Box 109, Folder 20)
  Bruce, WI
- Minnesota Joint Board and Gordon & Ferguson Co., 1961-1986 (Box 109, Folder 21)
  Minneapolis, MN
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board and Gouz (Elmont), 1974-1980 (Box 109, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board and Gouz (Freeport), 1977-1981 (Box 109, Folder 23)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Rubin Grais & Sons, 1976-1979 (Box 109, Folder 24)
- Winnipeg Joint Council, Local #459 and Great Northern Apparel, Inc. (GWG), 1980-1983 (Box 109, Folder 25)
- Minnesota Joint Board and Great Six Company, 1961-1973 (Box 109, Folder 26)
- Connecticut, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #115 and Nat Greenblatt's, 1959-1982 (Box 109, Folder 27)
- Massachusetts, Local #377 and Gro Togs, Inc., 1953-1966 (Box 109, Folder 28)
  New Bedford, MA
- Southern California Joint Board and H.K.S. Pants, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 29)
- Connecticut, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #115 and Ray Hammond Clothes, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 30)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Happy Time Industries, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 31)
- Minnesota Joint Board and B.W. Harris Manufacturing Co., 1983-1989 (Box 109, Folder 32)
  Bird Island, MN
- Minnesota Joint Board and B.W. Harris Manufacturing Co., 1980 (Box 109, Folder 33)
  Stillwater, MN
- Southern California Joint Board and Eddie Harth, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 34)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #926 and Hathaway Shirt Co., 1979 (Box 109, Folder 35)
- Alabama, Health-Tex (Guin Garment Corp.), 1959-1970 (Box 109, Folder 36)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Health-Tex, Inc., 1975-1978 (Box 109, Folder 37)
- South Carolina, Health-Tex, Inc., 1983-1988 (Box 109, Folder 38)
- New York Joint Board and Hirsch-Brody Ltd., 1978-1981 (Box 109, Folder 39)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #5 and Joe Hirsch, Inc., 1980-1985 (Box 109, Folder 40)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Hochenberg & Gelb, Inc., 1963 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Southern California Joint Board and Holly Hills Cleaners, 1976-1982 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Horizon Sportswear II, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- New York Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Hot Line Sportswear, Inc. (Sheridan Sportswear), 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and Hy-Grade Pants Co., 1961-1988 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and The Hub Company, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and The Hub Clothing, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Washington, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #71 and Hugo Wangel, Inc., 1961 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Capitol District, Local #188 and Bruce Hunt Stores, Inc., 1960-1971 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #969 and Hy's Men's Wear, Inc., 1972-1983 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board, Local #158 and I.S.L. Ltd., 1977 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Montreal Joint Board and Ideal Perfect Pad Ltd., 1967-1970 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Image Wear, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- United Shoe Workers of America and International Shoe Company, 1978-1982 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board, Local #158 and Israelis lax Ltd (I.S.L.), 1968-1974 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and J.A.C. Clothing Co., 1977 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and J.L. Clothing Co., 1977 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and J&W Coat, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Jackhammers, Inc., 1971-1978 (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Southern California Joint Board and Jacobson's, 1974-1983 (Box 110, Folder 20)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #559 and Lamppa Manufacturing Co., 1958-1982 (Box 110, Folder 21)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and J.J. Jones, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 22)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, Local #259 and Janesville Apparel Company, 1965-1969 (Box 110, Folder 23)
- Connecticut, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #115 and Joseph's of Waterbury, 1962-1974 (Box 110, Folder 24)
- New York Joint Board and Joseph's Boys' and Men's, 1979 (Box 110, Folder 25)
- New York Joint Board and K & H Tailoring, Inc., 1981 (Box 110, Folder 26)
- New York Joint Board and K.H.K. Custom Tailoring Co., 1978 (Box 110, Folder 27)
- Southern California Joint Board and K.W.B. Manufacturing Co., 1972-1976 (Box 110, Folder 28)
- Connecticut, Local #125 and Kaufman Shirt Co., 1940-1966 (Box 110, Folder 29)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Kayser-Roth Men's Apparel, 1982-1983 (Box 110, Folder 30)
- New York Joint Board and Kaysons Men's Wear, Inc., 1981-1988 (Box 110, Folder 31)
- New York Joint Board and Ken-Adams, Inc., 1977 (Box 110, Folder 32)
- New York Joint Board and Kenscott Sportswear, Inc., 1966-1982 (Box 110, Folder 33)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Keystone Uniform Manufacturing Co., 1977 (Box 110, Folder 34)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Kings Image, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 35)
- Shoe Division, Local #217A and Kinney Shoe Corporation, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 36)
- Milwaukee Joint Board and Harry Kleinschmidt, 1966-1969 (Box 110, Folder 37)
- Mississippi, Knickerbocker Manufacturing Company, 1962-1966 (Box 110, Folder 38)
- Massachusetts, Local #177 and Knopf Sportswear Co., 1956-1969 (Box 110, Folder 39)
- Tennessee, Knox Manufacturing Corp., 1954-1980 (Box 110, Folder 40)
- Western Ontario Joint Board and Kraven Knitting Ltd., 1976 (Box 110, Folder 41)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and George Kurland, 1958-1966 (Box 110, Folder 42)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and L.A. Shirt Company, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Boston Joint Board and L.S. Tailoring Company, 1960-1965 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Lagrange Park Jack's Men's Shops, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Abe Lacoff, 1958-1966 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board, Local #746 and Lake Manufacturing Co, Inc., 1959-1963 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #197 and Lakeland Manufacturing Co., 1967-1986 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Washington, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local # 71 and Lambo & Robey, 1961 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Laminates Unlimited, Inc., 1985 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Vancouver, Local #178 and Lancer of Canada Ltd., 1978-1979 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Southern California Joint Board and Lane Cleaners, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Lanza Tailors, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Larrimare Ltd., 1977 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Massachusetts, Local #187 and Lawrence Garment Co. & London Garment Co., 1972-1976 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Scranton & Wilkes-Barre District Joint Board and The Lazarus Store, Inc., 1968-1973 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Southern California Joint Board and Leader Cleaners, 1976-1982 (Box 111, Folder 15)
- New York Joint Board and Leading Male, 1978-1981 (Box 111, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Lebowitz & Nobles Sons, Inc., 1981 (Box 111, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and Neil Lee Apparel, Inc., 1979 (Box 111, Folder 18)
- New York, Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Ivy Lee Ltd., 1975 (Box 111, Folder 19)
- New York Joint Board and Leighton's, Inc., 1981 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  Bushelmen's
- New York Joint Board, Local #400 and Leighton's, Inc., 1981 (Box 111, Folder 21)
- New York Joint Board and Lemans, 1971-1978 (Box 111, Folder 22)
- Montreal Joint Board and Les Industries Gan-Don Ltd., 1980 (Box 111, Folder 23)
- Montreal Joint Board and Les Pantalons du Nord, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 111, Folder 24)
- Massachusetts, Lesnow Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1969 (Box 111, Folder 25)
- New York Joint Board, Local #162 and LeVanti Tailors (Cooper, Smith & Weiss), 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 26)
- New York Joint Board and Everett Levinsohn Corp., 1977 (Box 111, Folder 27)
- New Jersey, Local #126 and Leventhal Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1965-1983 (Box 111, Folder 28)
- New Jersey, Robert Lewis, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 29)
- Massachusetts, Local #353 and Lewiston Ltd., 1956-1962 (Box 111, Folder 30)
- Northwest Regional Joint Board, Local #74 and Liberty House, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 31)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Lico Corporation, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 32)
- Northwest Regional Joint Board, Local #74 and Lipman's, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 33)
- Minnesota Joint Board and M. Liman Co., 1976-1986 (Box 111, Folder 34)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #319 and Little Dutch Cleaners, 1978-1981 (Box 111, Folder 35)
- Montreal Joint Board and Little Nugget, Inc., 1977 (Box 111, Folder 36)
- Tennessee, Loretta Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1968 (Box 111, Folder 37)
- Montreal Joint Board and M.W. Jeans du Canada Ltd., 1977-1981 (Box 111, Folder 38)
- Mississippi, Macon Pants Corporation, 1959-1976 (Box 111, Folder 39)
- National Trouser Association and Main Pants, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 40)
- New York Joint Board and Majestic Trousers Co., Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 111, Folder 41)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and S. Makransky, Inc., 1977 (Box 111, Folder 42)
- Southern Organizational Department and Manhattan Industries, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 111, Folder 43)
  Jesup, GA
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Manhattan Ward, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 44)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Mannex Cravats, 1958-1967 (Box 111, Folder 45)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Mansco International, Inc., 1961-1970 (Box 111, Folder 46)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Mar Gaye, Inc., 1966 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Mar Gee, Inc., 1966 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- New York Joint Board and Billy Marcus, Ltd., 1978-1979 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  Bushelmen's Agreement
- Montreal Joint Board and Marimac, Inc., 1981 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and Martin-Burns, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board and Joe Martin Sportswear, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Connecticut, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #115 and Richard Martin of Westport, 1975-1977 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- New Jersey, Local #126 and Matan Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1958-1969 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #1 and #181 and Frank Mattie & Co., Inc., 1977-1987 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Rochester Joint Board and McFarlin's, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Rochester Joint Board, Clothing Sales People's Local #540 and McFarlin's, 1974-1977 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  Sales
- Cincinnati Joint Board and MacGregor (Brunswick Corp.), 1967-1976 (Box 112, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, General Office and McGregor-Doniger Corp., 1953-1958 (Box 112, Folder 13)
- General Office and McGregor-Doniger, Inc., 1959-1974 (Box 112, Folder 14)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, General Office and McGregor-Doniger, Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 112, Folder 15)
- License Agreements, McGregor-Doniger, Inc., 1974-1984 (Box 112, Folder 16)
- Northwest Regional Joint Board, Journeymen Tailors' Union Local #74 and Meier & Frank, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 17)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Leonard Mendelssohn, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 112, Folder 18)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Mercer Clothing Manufacturing, Inc., 1955-1965 (Box 112, Folder 19)
- New York Joint Board and Mern's, Inc., 1981 (Box 112, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Michael, Inc., 1977-1987 (Box 112, Folder 21)
- Miss. Joint Board and Mid-State Sportswear, Inc., 1976 (Box 112, Folder 22)
- New York Joint Board and Thomas Miller Menswear, Ltd., 1977-1981 (Box 112, Folder 23)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Miranda Brothers & Co., Inc., 1954-1970 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  International Report
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Model Glove Co., 1966 (Box 112, Folder 25)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Modern Cloth Sponging, 1968-1977 (Box 112, Folder 26)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Modern Filters, Inc., 1980-1985 (Box 112, Folder 27)
- Lehigh Valley Clothing Workers joint Board and Modern Slack Creations, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 112, Folder 28)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board and Mohawk Products, Inc., 1961-1970 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Montreal Joint Board, Local #274 and Morris Atlas Manufacturing co., Ltd., 1972-1975 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Consolidated Glove Cutters and Shavers Union Local #1714 and Mossetti Glove Co., Inc., 1967 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board and Moyer Pants Co., Inc., 1975-1979 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and Mr. Guy, Ltd., 1981-1985 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board and Thomas Murray, Inc., 1981 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and S. Nadelman Co., 1966 (Box 113, Folder 7)